David Pincheira

Buenos aires, Argentina · https://www.linkedin.com/in/dpincheira92/ · +54 299 5229656· davidpincheira92@gmail.com

I have more than 5 years of experience as a software developer. I have worked on a variety of projects for startups and big companies improving the code adding features for a better experience of the users. At the moment I am studying on a daily basis, in depth, the data structures and algorithms to keep up to date in technology while working as a backend developer for Grupo Hasar.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SymbarBuenos aires, ArgentinaBackend DeveloperOctober 2024–Present

- I am responsible for giving software solutions to different clients, helping to optimize tasks, new requirements and improving queries.
- I was also in charge of finishing the migration of the main software and I implemented the new interface improving the experience of the users. Here we work with PHP and SQL Server.

Outside The CubeBuenos aires, ArgentinaFull Stack DeveloperOctober 2022–July 2023

- I worked with the team deciding on customer requirements, in that case a big medical institution. So we were in charge of creating new views, functions and making API integrations for the main software of the company.
- I worked with laravel, jquery, CI/CD, GCP and Docker.

Satoshi Tango

Full Stack Developer

Buenos aires, Argentina

June 2021–September 2022

- My main tasks were in Php and I participated in the integration of new cryptocurrencies and different functions improving the experience of the user.
- I worked in integration of MercadoPago to charge money by credit card into the account of the users marking an important point in the crypto market.
- I developed the integration of third parties to improve the security of the cryptocurrencies for the banks asked by the banco industrial (BIND), the entity of regulations in Argentina. There, I developed anti-fraud solutions for the app.
- I started to create a dashboard to have all the partners in a new application because the company wanted to offer a new kind of business (B2B)
- The main technologies used were Php (Laravel), Angular, docker and MySQL

QUALIFICATIONS

UNIVERSIDAD ADVENTISTA DEL PLATA

Bachelor Degree in Information Systems

Entre Ríos, Argentina

May 2019

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- I have certificates in Nodejs(2022), Angular(2023) and Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate (2020)
- I am native speaker in Spanish and I have a B1-B2 level in English